Shoumik Rouf

27, East Ahmadnagar, Mirpur-1, Dhaka-1216



shoumikrouf14@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/shoumikr



01776633121



https://github.com/shoumik121

Summary

Like any product/project manager would, I take care of web products such as a website or an app. To help the product to grow in the likings of the consumers, I make creative marketing plans & strategies based on the data I get from Google analytics & Google Tag Manager. I'm very familiar with search engine optimization tools(Google Trends) & have over two year of experience in keyword research. I manage contents, Reports(GA4) & notifications on a regular basis and have the full knowledge of handling a content management system. I also have previous experience in web designing & capable of creating necessary design solutions.

Experience



Product Manager

MoMAGIC Bangladesh Ltd.

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021 (3 months)

I was working with the business team on a web media website "Browseit.com.bd". Here I used Google Analytics 4, Google Trends(SEO tool), Google Tag Manger & Excel Sheets to keep track of the websites data and update the daily report. Also generated Push Notifications based on web analytics to improve organic viewership.

JOB RESPONSIBILITIES:

Created thumbnails & banners

Content management system

Research keywords & help content to rank

Prepared push notifications

Track business using analytics

Improve website performance

Create daily report

or Full Stack Engineer

Dynamicflow

Jul 2021 - Sep 2021 (3 months)

JOB RESPONSIBILITIES:

Full Stack Web Development

Project Proposal Creation

Handling clients overseas

Research with Web Technologies



Engineer Intern

Mistri Solutions May 2021 - Jul 2021 (3 months) JOB RESPONSIBILITIES:

Key Word Research Web Theme Customization User Interface & Experience Design Develop Website Ideas & discuss Agile Business Strategies

Web Developer

(Freelance)

Dec 2021 - Present (3 months +)

The employer wanted me to make them a website for their farm.

The website is made using WordPress. Waiting for their requirement response.

URL: https://www.sikderagriorganicaltd.com/

Education



University of Asia Pacific

Bachelor of Science (BSc), Computer Science & Engineering, Computer Science 2017 - 2021

University of Asia Pacific - Bangladesh (2021)

Cumulative Average: 3.55 out of 4.00

Courses covered:

- 1. Database Systems Microsoft SQL Server & SQLite
- 2. Object Oriented Programming Java, python, C++
- 3. Object Oriented Programming II Visual and Web Programming
- -Html, CSS & JavaScript
- 4. Software Engineering -Python, PHP, Django & Bootstrap
- 5. Computer Networks Cisco Packet Tracer
- 6. Software Development Unity & Selenium
- 7. Artificial Intelligence and Expert Systems Prolog, Tensor Flow
- 8. Compiler Design & Computer Graphics OpenGL

THESIS:

On the circumstance of Bangladesh Smoke Object Segmentation Based on Surveillance Videos Using Deep Learning.



🕼 DRMC - Dhaka Residential Model College

Higher Secondary School, Science

2013 - 2015

Mohammadpur, Dhaka(1207)

Cumulative Average: 5.00 out of 5.00



🗶 DRMC - Dhaka Residential Model College

Secondary School, Science

2011 - 2013

Mohammadpur, Dhaka(1207)

Phone: +880258153774 Email: drmc_bd@yahoo.com

Cumulative Average: 5.00 out of 5.00

Skills

Research • Business • Networking • Online Marketing • Google Analytics • Google Tag Manager • Google Workspace • Web Development • Machine Learning • Artificial Intelligence (AI)

References

1. Molla Rashied Hussein

Assistant Professor,
Department of Computer Science
Institute: University of Asia Pacific
Contact: +8801912703756
Email: mrh.cse@uap-bd.edu

2. Dr. Abu Shara Shamsur Rouf

Professor Department of Pharmaceutical Technology Faculty of Pharmacy, Dhaka University Email: rouf321@yahoo.com Phone: Tel: 9661900~59; Extn. 8181 (Off)

Declaration

I do hereby certify that all the above statements and information provided are authentic.

